Dor Tsivion

Qa Engineer with ISTQB foundation

Profile

Highly motivated and driven desire to develop and learn in QA Engineering. Recent management experience that requires interpersonal communication, delegation, and prioritization. My technical skills and aptitudes include SQL Servers, HTML, CSS languages, Writing STP, STR, and STD documents, testing software, Linux and Windows operating systems, and JavaScript.

Employment History

Quality Assurance Engineer At "Beach Bum", Raanana

March 2020 - Present

- Manage all communications related to QA Status on a daily basis during execution.
 Reporting potential risks during all any stages of development lifecycle
- Work closely with the development team to test systems for defects using Scrum, Kanban and other Agile/Lean methodologies
- Using existing tools and techniques to execute test cases and build/script new tools for performing testing/validation function
- Perform business and system analysis; provide recommendations for process improvement
- Provide daily/weekly reports to manager
- Works closely with development manager to creates and/or contributes to test plans and test procedures

Restaurant manager, Rishon Le Zion

November 2018 — January 2020

- Utilize excellent interpersonal communication when working with staff while also providing expert customer service to patrons.
- Cope with a high pressure environment.

Management responsibilities for approximately 40 employees including

 arranging work schedules, training staff, managing events, booking and staging events, and providing customer service.

Education

Foundation ISTQB, John Bryce College, Tel Aviv

November 2019

student in the QA Software Testing Course in the Foundation ISTQB.

Comprehensive High School Mekif H, Rishon Le Zion

January 2009 — July 2013

Full matriculation science class that includes anatomy and physiology 10 Kamis.

Army Service

November 2013 — November 2016

- Full combat service in combat intelligence unit.
- Responsible for approximately 120 medical fighters. Appointment scheduling, referrals, follow-ups, reports, field training, harness training, and more.
- Managed a team of 7 departmental paramedics and taught professional classes.
- Coped with high pressure conditions to meet goals.

Details

Ateret Zahav , Rishon Le Zion, 7571406, Israel, 0528829191 Tsiviondor@gmail.com

Date of birth 22/07/1995

Nationality Israeli

Links

Linkedin

Skills

Depth experience with server -In client systems and database SQL server.

Knowledge of html, CSS languages

Writing STP, STR, STD documents

Testing software: Quality
Center, Microsoft Test
Management, QTP knowledge

Full control of Linux and Windows operating systems

Control of test methodologies

Java script familiarity and work with development tools, familiarity with basic commands, and simple procedure plannin

Languages

Hebrew - Native speaker

English - Professional working proficiency